<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<addons>

<addon id="repository.amazon" name="arabiflix repo" version="2.5" provider-name="arabiflix">
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.repository" name="arabiflix repo">
    <dir>
        <info compressed="false">https://raw.githubusercontent.com/arabiflix/repository.amazon/master/leia/addons.xml</info>
        <checksum>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/arabiflix/repository.amazon/master/leia/addons.xml.md5</checksum>
        <datadir zip="true">https://raw.githubusercontent.com/arabiflix/repository.amazon/master/leia</datadir>
    </dir>
    <dir>
        <info compressed="false">https://raw.githubusercontent.com/Gujal00/smrzips/master/addons.xml</info>
        <checksum>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/Gujal00/smrzips/master/addons.xml.md5</checksum>
        <datadir zip="true">https://raw.githubusercontent.com/Gujal00/smrzips/master/zips/</datadir>
    </dir>
    <dir>
        <info compressed="false">https://raw.githubusercontent.com/a4k-openproject/repository.openscrapers/master/zips/addons.xml</info>
        <checksum>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/a4k-openproject/repository.openscrapers/master/zips/addons.xml.md5</checksum>
        <datadir zip="true">https://raw.githubusercontent.com/a4k-openproject/repository.openscrapers/master/zips/</datadir>
    </dir>
    </extension>
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
        <summary>Testing and Learning stuff</summary>
        <description>arabiflix repo</description>
        <platform>all</platform>
    </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="plugin.video.theamazon" name="TheAmazon" provider-name="arabiflix" version="2.2.5">
	<requires>
		<import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.20.0" />
		<import addon="script.theamazon.artwork" />
		<import addon="script.theamazon.metadata" />
		<import addon="script.module.resolveurl" />
		<import addon="script.module.requests" />
		<import addon="script.module.metahandler" />
		<import addon="script.module.beautifulsoup4" />
		<import addon="script.module.amazonscrapers" />
		<import addon="script.module.openscrapers" optional="true" />
		<import addon="script.module.orion" optional="true" />
	</requires>
	<extension library="theamazon.py" point="xbmc.python.pluginsource">
		<provides>video</provides>
	</extension>
	<extension library="service.py" point="xbmc.service" start="startup" />
	<extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
		<reuselanguageinvoker>false</reuselanguageinvoker>
		<summary lang="en_GB">theamazon</summary>
		<description lang="en_GB">Multi-source and multi-scraper package add-on. A basic scraper pack is provided but also supports Openscrapers, and native Orion integration.[CR][CR]The author does not host any of the content in this add-on and takes no responsibility for content found.</description>
		<platform>all</platform>
		<license>GNU GENERAL PUBLIC LICENSE. Version 3, 29 June 2007</license>
		<forum />
		<website />
		<source />
		<disclaimer lang="en_GB">The author of this add-on does not host any of the content which is found and has no affiliation with any of the content providers. This add-on simply searches websites for content. Use at your own risk!</disclaimer>
		<assets>
			<icon>icon.png</icon>
			<fanart>fanart.jpg</fanart>
		</assets>
		<news>
- See Changelog on Tools menu
		</news>
	</extension>
</addon>

<addon id="script.theamazon.artwork" version="1.0.7" name="TheAmazon Artwork" provider-name="arabiflix">
	<requires>
		<import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.19.0"/>
	</requires>
	<extension point="xbmc.python.module" library="lib" />
	<extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
		<summary>Themes for the theamazon Addon</summary>
		<description></description>
		<platform>all</platform>
	</extension>
</addon>

<addon id="script.theamazon.metadata" version="1.0.2" name="TheAmazon Metadata" provider-name="arabiflix">
	<requires>
		<import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.19.0"/>
	</requires>
	<extension point="xbmc.python.module" library="lib" />
	<extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
		<summary>Metadata for the theamazon Addon</summary>
		<description>Metadata for theamazon are maintained separately to make distribution of the the addon itself easier/faster.</description>
		<platform>all</platform>
	</extension>
</addon>

<addon id="script.module.amazonscrapers" name="AmazonScrapers Module" version="0.7.2" provider-name="TheAmazon">
    <requires>
        <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.1.0" />
        <import addon="script.module.beautifulsoup4" />
        <import addon="script.module.requests" />
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.python.module" library="lib" />
    <extension point="xbmc.python.pluginsource" library="lib/default.py">
        <provides>executable</provides>
    </extension>
        <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
            <platform>all</platform>
            <summary lang="en">AmazonScrapers Module</summary>
            <description>Scrape common video host for URL's to be playable in Kodi, simplifying addon development of video plugins requiring multi video hosts.</description>
                <disclaimer lang="en">The author is not responsible for the use of this addon. The author is not responsible for the content found using this addon. The author does not host or own any content found within this addon.[CR]The author is in no way affiliated with Kodi, Team Kodi, or the XBMC Foundation.[CR]This is a Non-profit resource, organized solely for educational purposes which is protected under the Fair-Use doctrine of the Copyright Act, Specifically section 107, which does promote freedom of expression, by permitting the unlicensed use of copyright-protected works.</disclaimer>
    <platform>all</platform>
    <license>GNU GENERAL PUBLIC LICENSE. Version 3, 29 June 2007</license>
    <assets>
        <icon>icon.png</icon>
        <fanart></fanart>
    </assets>
    <news></news>
    </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="script.module.metahandler" 
     name="metahandler" 
     version="3.0.3" 
     provider-name="Eldorado, jsergio">
  <requires>
    <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.1.0" />
    <import addon="script.module.simplejson" version="3.3.0"/>
    <import addon="script.module.addon.common" version="2.0.0"/>
    <import addon="script.module.myconnpy" version="1.1.6"/>
  </requires>
  <extension point="xbmc.python.module" library="lib" />
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
    <summary lang="en">Downloads Artwork for TV shows, Movies and Music videos for addons and stores them in a local SQLITE database</summary>
    <description lang="en">Queries, stores, and returns metadata for TV shows, Movies and Musicvideos. [CR]Sources:[CR]www.thetvdb.com[CR]www.themoviedb.org[CR]www.imdb.com[CR]www.omdbapi.com[CR]This product uses the TMDb API but is not endorsed or certified by TMDb.</description>
    <disclaimer lang="en"></disclaimer>
    <language></language>
    <platform>all</platform>
    <license>GNU GENERAL PUBLIC LICENSE. Version 2, June 1991</license>
    <forum></forum>
    <website></website>
    <email></email>
    <source></source>
  </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="script.module.lambdascrapers" name="Lambdascrapers Module" version="1.8.0i" provider-name="I-A-C">
	<requires>
		<import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.1.0" />
		<import addon="script.module.beautifulsoup4"/>
	</requires>
	<extension point="xbmc.python.module" library="lib" />
	<extension point="xbmc.python.pluginsource" library="lib/default.py">
		<provides>executable</provides>
	</extension>
	<!--<extension point="xbmc.service" library="CleanupService.py" start="startup" />-->
		<extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
			<platform>all</platform>
			<summary lang="en">Lambdascrapers Module</summary>
			<description>Scrape common video host for URL's to be playable in XBMC/Kodi, simplifying addon development of video plugins requiring multi video hosts.</description>
        		<disclaimer lang="en_GB">The author is not responsible for the use of this addon. The author is not responsible for the content found using this addon. The author does not host or own any content found within this addon.[CR]The author is in no way affiliated with Kodi, Team Kodi, or the XBMC Foundation.[CR]This is a Non-profit resource, organized solely for educational purposes which is protected under the Fair-Use doctrine of the Copyright Act, Specifically section 107, which does promote freedom of expression, by permitting the unlicensed use of copyright-protected works.</disclaimer>
        		<license>Beerware rev. 42</license>
		</extension>
</addon>

<addon id="script.module.orion" version="4.2.3" name="Orion" provider-name="Orion">
	<requires>
		<import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.1.0"/>
		<import addon="repository.orion" version="1.0.0" optional="true" />
	</requires>
	<extension point="xbmc.python.pluginsource" library="lib/addon.py">
		<provides>executable</provides>
	</extension>
	<extension point="xbmc.python.module" library="lib" /> <!-- Must be placed after xbmc.python.pluginsource, otherwise the addon does not show in the repository. -->
	<extension point="xbmc.service" library="lib/service.py" start="startup" />
	<extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
		<summary lang="en">Torrent, Usenet, and Hoster Providers</summary>
		<description lang="en">Orion is a system for caching search and scraping results for later reuse. Metadata and links on Orion are maintained by the community. Searches are cached so that subsequent users can quickly access the results without having to go through a lengthy scraping process themselves. The Orion Kodi addon does not provide any search or playback features, but it can easily be integrated into any other addon, website, or standalone program with minimal effort.</description>
		<disclaimer lang="en">Orion does not create, host, or distribute any files or videos. Orion is a caching service providing low-level API access to a community-maintained storage of textual data. All metadata and links available through Orion are scraped, processed, and submitted by community users. Due to the volume, velocity, and complexity of the data, Orion cannot inspect or validate the content submitted by users. Data on Orion may therefore be inaccurate, out-dated, or in other ways unusable. Orion does not guarantee the validity or integrity of the data available through its API and does not take liability for any of the data submitted by its users. Users take the risk and are responsible for the manner in which they utilize the Orion API.</disclaimer>
		<platform>all</platform>
		<license>GPL 3.0</license>
		<website>https://orionoid.com</website>
		<forum>https://support.orionoid.com</forum>
		<assets>
			<icon>icon.png</icon>
			<fanart>fanart.jpg</fanart>
		</assets>
	</extension>
</addon>

<addon id="service.subtitles.subscene2"
       name="Subscene.com(2)"
       version="1.7.2.7"
       provider-name="CrowleyAJ, thuongtin.com">
    <requires>
        <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.1.0"/>
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.subtitle.module"
               library="service.py"/>
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
        <summary lang="en">Get subtitles from Subscene.com</summary>
        <description lang="en">Subscene.com provides subtitles in more than 50 languages, mainly in English, Arabic, Brazilian Portuguese, Farsi, Indonesian and Vietnamese.
Other languages with a great number of subtitles are: Danish, French, Swedish, Dutch, Italian, Norwegian and Spanish.</description>
        <disclaimer lang="en"/>
        <platform>all</platform>
        <language/>
        <license>GNU GENERAL PUBLIC LICENSE. Version 2, June 1991</license>
        <forum>http://forum.xbmc.org/showthread.php?tid=184854</forum>
        <website/>
        <email/>
        <source>https://github.com/manacker/service.subtitles.subscene</source>
    </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="script.keymapedit" name="Keymap Edit" provider-name="takoi, arabiflix" version="0.1.3">
    <requires>
        <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.19.0" />
    </requires>
    <extension library="main.py" point="xbmc.python.script" />
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
        <summary lang="en_GB">An editor for keymap files</summary>
        <description lang="en_GB">Keymap Edit is a GUI for configuring mappings for remotes, keyboard and other inputs supported by xbmc. Note: existing user defined key mappings will be removed.[CR][I]This is a Keymap Editor fork. Credit goes to original creator (takoi)[/I]</description>
        <platform>all</platform>
        <language />
        <license>GNU GENERAL PUBLIC LICENSE. Version 3, 29 June 2007</license>
        <forum />
        <source>https://github.com/arabiflix/repository.amazon/leia/script.keymapedit</source>
        <news>[I]Changes on this fork include:[/I]
- Forked - Rebranded to Keymap Edit
- Added some missing actions, categories, windows introduced in Kodi v17 and v18
- Generated .xml is now properly indented, instead of 1 line
- Some rephrasing
- Fixed keymap reloading after save
- Converted to current language formatting
- Added Greek language
        </news>
    </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="service.subtitles.opensubtitles_by_opensubtitles"
       name="OpenSubtitles.org by OpenSubtitles"
       version="5.2.14"
       provider-name="amet, opensubtitles">
  <requires>
    <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.1.0"/>
  </requires>
  <extension point="xbmc.subtitle.module"
             library="service.py" />
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
    <summary>OpenSubtitles by OpenSubtitles.org</summary>
    <summary lang="hr">OpenSubtitles.org podnaslovi</summary>
    <description lang="en">Anonymously search and download subtitles for movies and TV-Series from OpenSubtitles.org without log-in. Search in 75 languages, 4.000.000+ subtitles, daily updates. </description>
	<description lang="at">Pelis and Subtítulos TV en munches llingües, milenta de subtítulos traducíos y xubíos caldía. Descarga llibre dende la fonte, sofitu API, millones d'usuarios.</description>
	<description lang="br">Istitloù Filmoù ha TV e meur a yezh, miliadoù a istitloù troet hag uskarget bemdez. Pellgargadenn digoust diouzh ar vammenn, skoazell an API, millionoù a implijerien.</description>
	<description lang="ca">Subtítols de films i televisió en múltiples idiomes, milers de subtítols traduïts carregats diàriament. Descàrrega gratuïta des de la font, suport de l'API, amb milions d'usuaris.</description>
	<description lang="cs">Titulky k filmům a seriálům v mnoha jazycích, denně tisíce nahraných přeložených titulků. Stažení zadarmo přímo od zdroje, podpora API, milióny uživatelů.</description>
	<description lang="de">Film- und TV-Untertitel in vielen Sprachen, täglicher Upload von tausenden übersetzten Untertiteln. Freier Download von der Quelle, API-Unterstützung, Millionen Nutzer</description>
	<description lang="el">Ταινίες και Σειρές σε όλες τις γλώσσες, χιλιάδες μεταφρασμένοι υπότιτλοι ανεβαίνουν καθημερινά, κατεβάστε δωρεάν , υποστήριξη API από εκατομμύρια χρήστες</description>
	<description lang="eo">Filmaj kaj Televidaj subtekstoj en multaj lingvoj, miloj da tradukitaj subtekstoj ĉiutage alŝutataj. Senpaga elŝuto de fonto, API-subteno, miloj da uzantoj.</description>
	<description lang="es">Películas y Subtítulos en diversos idiomas, miles de subtítulos traducidos subidos diariamente. Descarge gratis, soporte API, millones de usuarios.</description>
	<description lang="et">Sadu Filmi ja TV Serjaalide subtiitrid erinevates keeltes laetakse üles igapäev. tasuta allalaadimine ja abi, rohkem kui miljon kasutajat.</description>
	<description lang="eu">Film eta Telebista azpitituluak hizkuntza anitzetan, milaka azpititulu itzuliak igotzen dira egunero. Doan jaitsi iturburutik, API sostengua, milioika erabiltzaile.</description>
	<description lang="fi">Tekstityksiä useilla kielillä elokuviin ja TV-Sarjoihin, tuhansia uusia tekstityksiä päivittäin, ilmainen lataus, API tuki, miljoonia käyttäjiä.</description>
	<description lang="fr">Les sous-titres de film et téléfilm en plusieurs langues, des milliers de sous-titres traduits tous les jours. Bénéficiez de téléchargements gratuits depuis la source, du support API, une d'une communauté de millions d'utilisateurs.</description>
	<description lang="hi">मूवी और टीवी उपशीर्षक कई भाषाओं में अनुवाद उपशीर्षक के हजारों दैनिक अपलोड की गई। मुफ्त डाउनलोड स्रोत से , एपीआई समर्थन, उपयोगकर्ताओं के लाखों लोगों की ।</description>
	<description lang="hr">Anonimno pretraživajte i preuzimajte podnaslove za filmove i TV serije sa OpenSubtitles.org bez prijave, pretraga za 75 jezika. Dostupni milijuni podnaslova, uz svakodnevno dodavanje novih podnaslova.</description>
	<description lang="hu">Film és TV feliratok több nyelven, naponta több ezer lefordított felirat feltöltés. Ingyenes letöltés a forrástól, API támogatás, több millió felhasználó.</description>
	<description lang="id">Subjudul film dan serial TV dalam multibahasa, ribuan subjudul diterjemah dan diunggah setiap harinya. Pengunduhan gratis dari sumber, didukung fitur antarmuka pemrograman aplikasi, dan jutaan pengguna.</description>
	<description lang="is">Textar fyrir myndir og sjónvarpsþ. á mörgum tungumálum, þúsundir af þýddum textum upphlaðið daglega. Frítt niðurhal frá síðu, API stuðningur, milljónir notenda.</description>
	<description lang="it">Sottotitoli di Film e TV in più lingue,migliaia di sottotitoli tradotti caricati ogni giorno.Download gratuito,supporto API, milioni di utenti.</description>
	<description lang="ja">映画やテレビの字幕をさまざまな言語で。毎日数多くの翻訳字幕がアップロードされています。ソースを無料ダウンロード、API 対応、数百万を超えるユーザー。</description>
	<description lang="ka">სუბტიტრები ფილმებისა და ტვ-სთვის მრავალ ენაზე. ათასობიტ თარგმნილი სუბტიტრის ატვირთვა ყოველდღიურად. უდასო ჩამოტვირტვა წყაროდან, API მხარდაჭერა, მილიონობით მომხმარებელი</description>
	<description lang="km">អត្ថបទរឿងសម្រាប់ ខ្សែភាពយន្ត និងកម្មវិធីទូរទស្សន៍​ ជាភាសាជាច្រើន រួមនឹងអត្ថបទរឿងបកប្រែរាប់ពាន់​រឿង​ដែល​ត្រូវបាន​អ័ពឡូដជារៀងរាល់ថ្ងៃ។ ទាញយកដោយឥតគិតថ្លៃពីប្រភពដើម គាំទ្រ API និងមានអ្នកប្រើប្រាស់រាប់លាននាក់។ </description>
	<description lang="ko">Movie and TV Subtitles in multiple languages, thousands of translated subtitles uploaded daily. Free download from source, API support, millions of users.</description>
	<description lang="ms">Sarikata TV dan Movie dalam pelbagai bahasa, ribuan terjemahan sarikata dimuat-naik setiap hari.Muat-turun percuma dari sumber utama, sokongan API, jutaan pengguna.</description>
	<description lang="nl">Ondertitels voor films en tv-series in meerdere talen, dagelijks upload van duizenden vertaalde ondertitels. Gratis downloaden van de bron, API ondersteuning, miljoenen gebruikers.</description>
	<description lang="no">Undertekster for film og TV på mange språk, med tusener av nye oversettelser hver dag. Vi har gratis nedlasting av undertekster, API-support, og mange millioner brukere.</description>
	<description lang="pt-br">Milhares de legendas para filmes e seriados de TV, em vários idiomas, são traduzidas e enviadas diariamente. Download grátis, suporte API e milhões de usuários.</description>
	<description lang="pl">Napisy do filmów i seriali w wielu językach. Tysiące napisów dodawanych codziennie. Darmowe pobranie, miliony użytkowników.</description>
	<description lang="pt">Legendas de filmes e séries de TV em vários idiomas, milhares de legendas traduzidas e enviadas diariamente. Download grátis a partir da fonte, suporte API, milhões de utilizadores.</description>
	<description lang="ro">Subtitrari pentru filme in multe limbi, mii de subtitrari traduse si încărcate in fiecare zi. Descărca gratuit de la sursă, suport API, milioane de utilizatori.</description>
	<description lang="ru">Кино и ТВ субтитры на нескольких языках, тысячи переведенными субтитрами загружены ежедневно. Бесплатно скачать из исходных текстов, поддержка API, миллионы пользователей.</description>
	<description lang="sk">Titulky pre filmy a TV seriály, denne nahratých tisíce titulkov preložených vo viacerých jazykoch. Sťahuj zadarmo zo zdroja, podpora API, milióny používateľov.</description>
	<description lang="sl">Filmski in televizijski podnapisi v mnogo jezikih, na tisoče prevedenih podnapisov dnevno. Brezplačen prenos iz vira, podpora API, miljoni uporabnikov.</description>
	<description lang="sq">Titra filmash dhe serialesh në shumë gjuhë, mijëra titra të përkthyera që vendosen çdo ditë. Shkarko nga burimi, apo nga mbështetja e API-së, miliona përdorues.</description>
	<description lang="sr">Titlovi za filmove i TV na mnogim jezicima, hiljade prevoda okačenih svakodnevno. Besplatno skidanje sa izvora, podrška za API, milioni korisnika.</description>
	<description lang="sv">Filmer och Tv-undertexter med olika språk, tusentals översatta undertexter uppladdade dagligen. Gratis nerladdning från källor, API support, miljoner av användare.</description>
	<description lang="tr">Her gün eklenen, pek çok dildeki binlerce film ve dizi altyazısı. Kaynağından ücretsiz indirme, API desteği ve milyonlarca kullanıcı.</description>
	<description lang="uz">Film va TV Taglavhalari ko'p tillarda, minglab tarjima qilingan taglavhalar har kuni tizimga yuklanadi. Bepul resursdan yuklab oling, API qo'llaydi, millionlab foydalanuvchilar.</description>
	<description lang="zh">多语种的电影及剧集字幕，每日更新千余条翻译好的字幕。免费下载，提供API接口，已拥有上百万的用户。</description>
    <disclaimer>Works without log-in</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="hr">Radi bez prijave</disclaimer>
	<news>
Improved add-on by OpenSubtitles.org
v5.2.14 (2017-01-23)
- Users are able to download subtitles as anonymous without authentication. Added localized descriptions, media files
- New feature: Users are able to check for subtitles when Kodi is not playing, by using the manual search or by standing on an item and opening the subtitles search dialog (By key or by an external addon)  | @burekas
	</news>
    <platform>all</platform>
	<language></language>
    <license>GNU GENERAL PUBLIC LICENSE. Version 2, June 1991</license>
    <forum>https://forum.opensubtitles.org/viewtopic.php?f=8&amp;t=15847</forum>
    <website>http://www.opensubtitles.org</website>
    <email>admin [at] opensubtitles {dot} org</email>                                               
	<assets>
	    <icon>resources/media/os_logo_512x512.png</icon>
	    <fanart>resources/media/os_fanart.jpg</fanart>    
		<screenshot>resources/media/screenshot_1.jpg</screenshot>
		<screenshot>resources/media/screenshot_2.jpg</screenshot>
		<screenshot>resources/media/screenshot_3.jpg</screenshot>				
	</assets>
    <source>https://github.com/opensubtitles/service.subtitles.opensubtitles_by_opensubtitles</source>    
  </extension>
</addon>

</addons>
